<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on Pierre Vincent</title>
    <link>https://blog.pvincent.io/page/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on Pierre Vincent</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.pvincent.io/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Contributions on other publications</title>
      <link>https://blog.pvincent.io/page/contributions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.pvincent.io/page/contributions/</guid>
      <description> 2019 Integration tests don&amp;rsquo;t cut it for microservices. Here&amp;rsquo;s what does. (TechBeacon) How to move a large monolithic app to continuous delivery with zero downtime (TechBeacon) 2018 Software superstars lined up for this year&amp;rsquo;s RebelCon (Poppulo Tech Blog) Reaching production is only the beginning (Poppulo Tech Blog) 2016 Pact tests: what about state data? (Poppulo Tech Blog) Sharing Consumer-Driven Contracts with Pact Broker (Poppulo Tech Blog) 2015 Our take-away from µCon 2015, the Microservices conference (Poppulo Tech Blog) Microservices: Service Discovery with Smartstack and Docker (Poppulo Tech Blog) How to write clean functional code in Scala and keep it that way (Poppulo Tech Blog) Why you should use Consumer-Driven Contracts for Microservice integration tests (Poppulo Tech Blog) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Training &amp; speaking at events</title>
      <link>https://blog.pvincent.io/page/speaking/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2019 15:07:01 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.pvincent.io/page/speaking/</guid>
      <description>If the content on this blog or my talks have resonated with you, that&amp;rsquo;s the best thing I can hope for! If you&amp;rsquo;re interested in getting me to run a workshop/talk at your conference (or internally to your team), please do get in touch with me on speaking@pvincent.io.
Below are some example of workshops and talks that I&amp;rsquo;m currently running.
Workshops Cloud native monitoring with Prometheus &amp;amp; Grafana When it comes to monitoring tools in the Cloud Native space, Prometheus is definitely hard to miss.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>